
export const Question11to20 = [
    {
        Question: "What is GitHub?",
        Options: ['A social media platform', 'A code hosting platform for version control', 'A programming language', 'A database'],
        Answer: "A code hosting platform for version control"
    },
    {
        Question: "What is a repository in GitHub?",
        Options: ['A storage for project files', 'A function in a program', 'A type of database', 'A user profile'],
        Answer: "A storage for project files"
    },
    {
        Question: "What is the purpose of a pull request in GitHub?",
        Options: ['To submit contributions to a project', 'To delete a repository', 'To follow another user', 'To create a new branch'],
        Answer: "To submit contributions to a project"
    },
    {
        Question: "What is a branch in GitHub?",
        Options: ['A copy of the codebase where you can make changes', 'A type of issue', 'A user account', 'A commit message'],
        Answer: "A copy of the codebase where you can make changes"
    },
    {
        Question: "What is the main branch in a repository typically called?",
        Options: ['Primary', 'Main', 'Master', 'Head'],
        Answer: "Main"
    },
    {
        Question: "What does the command 'git clone' do?",
        Options: ['Copies a repository to your local machine', 'Deletes a repository', 'Creates a new branch', 'Merges two branches'],
        Answer: "Copies a repository to your local machine"
    },
    {
        Question: "What is a commit in GitHub?",
        Options: ['A record of changes made to the repository', 'A branch of a repository', 'A GitHub user', 'A repository setting'],
        Answer: "A record of changes made to the repository"
    },
    {
        Question: "What is GitHub Issues used for?",
        Options: ['Tracking bugs and feature requests', 'Managing user accounts', 'Storing code snippets', 'Creating repositories'],
        Answer: "Tracking bugs and feature requests"
    },
    {
        Question: "What is a fork in GitHub?",
        Options: ['A personal copy of someone else\'s repository', 'A type of branch', 'A repository setting', 'A GitHub user'],
        Answer: "A personal copy of someone else's repository"
    },
    {
        Question: "What is the purpose of a README file in a GitHub repository?",
        Options: ['To provide information about the project', 'To list all contributors', 'To store environment variables', 'To manage repository settings'],
        Answer: "To provide information about the project"
    }
];
